Guide to the Peter H.L. and Edith Chang Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Underwood, Felix J.
    - Underwood, Felix J. To Peter H. L. Chang, Mississippi 20/1/1937, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.25)
  - Wan, Fu-lin
    - Wan, Fu-lin To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An ] 1/3/[n.y.], (1 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 23.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Wan Fu-lin, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 23.01)
    - Wan, Fu-lin To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 23.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Wan Fu-lin, [Taiwan] [n.d.], (2 leaf autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 23.02)
  - Wan, Fu-min
    - Wan, Fu-min To Peter H. L. Chang, Liaoning 18/3/1991, (3 leaf, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 24)
  - Wang, Fu-shi
    - Wang, Fu-shi To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, Beijing,15/6/[n.y.], (2page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.05)
    - Wang Fu-shi To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei n.d., (1 page, autograph letter ) (Box 06, Folder 08.05)
    - Wang Fu-shi To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 3/7/1990, (1 page newspaper photocopy ) (Box 06, Folder 08.05)
  - Wang, Fu-zhou
    - Wang, Fu-zhou[also as Wang Fu-chow] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 11/1/[1937], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 25)
    - Wang, Fu-zhou To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 1/3/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 25)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, pages 38-39 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Wang, Fu-zhou To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 15/3/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 25)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 68 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Wang, Guan-wu
    - Wang, Guan-wu [also as Wang Kuan-wu] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Gu Shengzhou]7/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 26)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 44 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Wang, Guan-wu et al To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 20/2/[n.y.], (1 page, telegram ) (Box 04, Folder 26)
      [See Telegrams after Xi An [Box 6 Folder 15]: With 15 people listed: Wang Zhuo-ran, Song Xing-ta, Chen Xian-zhou, Ye Bi-liang, Yu Cheng-ze, Zhou Jing-wen, Wu Ou, Yang Wei-zhen, Du Qi-jie, Li Xi-geng, Zhang Ke-wei, Han Li-ru, Tian Yu-shi, Wang Chong-yu, Wang Guan-wu.]
  - Wang, Han-guang
    - Wang, Han-guang [also as Wang Han-kuang] To Liu Yi-guang, [n.p.] 15/4/[n.y.] (Box 04, Folder 27)
      [1 page, autograph letter signed]
  - Wang, Hong-zhi
    - Wang, Hong-zhi To Peter H. L. Chang, Liaoning 2/3/1995, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 01.08)
  - Wang, Hua-yi
    - Wang, Hua-yi To Peter H. L. Chang, [Peiping] 5/8/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 28)
  - Wang, Hui
    - Wang, Hui To Peter H. L. Chang, [Songjiang] 10/1/M26 [1937], (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 29)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, loose leaf [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Wang, Ju-ren
    - Wang, Ju-ren To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 06, Folder 07)
  - Wang, Ru-ling
    - Wang, Ru-ling To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.]/[n.m.]/1983, (1 autograph card ) (Box 06, Folder 01.01)
  - Wang, Xing-dong
    - Wang, Xing-dong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 19/2/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 07.08)
  - Wang, Yi-zhe
    - Wang, Yi-zhe [also as Wang Yi-che] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 30)
    - Wang, Yi-zhe To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 16/1/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 30)
      [See Ma Zhan-shan [Box 4]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Wang Yi-zhe, [Xikou] 19/[n.m.]/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 30)
  - Wang, Zhuo-ran
    - Wang, Zhuo-ran To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 1/3/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 31.01)
    - Wang, Zhuo-ran To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 10/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 31.01)
    - Wang, Zhuo-ran [also as Wang Cho-jan] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Shanghai]7/11/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 31.01)
    - Wang, Zhuo-ran et al To Peter H. L. Chang, Peiping 20/2[1937], (1 page, telegram ) (Box 04, Folder 31)
  - Warren, M. C.
    - Warren, M. C. To Peter H. L. Chang, Chungking 25/9/1939, (1 page, typed letter signed(with a calling card) ) (Box 06, Folder 06.26)
  - Wei, Dao-ming
    - Wei, Dao-ming [also as Wei Tao-ming] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Taipei]7/12/[n.y.], (1 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 32)
  - Wei, De-tang
    - Wei, De-tang [also as Wei The-t’ang] and Zhu Lian-qing [Chu Lian-ch’ing] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 8/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 33)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 64 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Wieser, Walter G.
    - Wieser, Walter G. To [Peter H. L. Chang], Wien, Austria 28/9/1989, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.27)
  - Women Alliance’s Garment Factory
    - Women Alliance’s Garment Factory To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.][n.d.], (1 autograph card signed. ) (Box 05, Folder 12)
    - Women Alliance’s Garment Factory To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.][n.d.], (1 page, typed letter signed [invitation] ) (Box 05, Folder 12)
  - Wu, Ding-chang
    - Wu, Ding-chang [Wu Ting-ch’ang] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Gui Zhou] 25/4/M29 [1940], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 34.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Wu Ding-chang, [n.p.] 19/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 34.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Wu Ding-chang, [n.p.] 17/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 34.02)
  - Wu, Jia-xiang
    - Wu, Jia-xiang To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An],10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 06, Folder 07)
  - Wu, Ke-ren
    - Wu, Ke-ren et al To Peter H. L. Chang, Pingliang 23/2/[1937], (6 page telegram ) (Box 06, Folder 07)
      [ See Telegrams after Xi An [Box 6 Folder 15]: With 5 signatures: Wu Ke-ren, Guo Xi-peng, Zhou Fu-cheng, Zhang Wen-qing, Jin Kui-bi.]
  - Wu, Shi-tian
    - Wu, Shi-tian To Peter H. L. Chang, Guangzhou 23/9/1990, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.06)
  - Wu, Tie-cheng
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Wu Tie-cheng [also as Wu Tieh-ch’eng], [n.p.] 18/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter (draft) ) (Box 04, Folder 35)
      [See Zhang Qun [Box 4]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Wu Tie-cheng, [n.p.] 17/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 35)
  - Xia Chang li
    - Xia Chang-Li To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 5/2/1993, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 01.09)
  - Xu, Xiang-ying
    - Xu, Xiang-ying To Peter H. L. Chang, Zhejiang 17/7/[n.y.], (2 leaf, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 01.10)
  - Xu, Yong-chang
    - Xu, Yong-chang [also as Hsu Yung-ch’ang] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.]7/2/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 37)
    - Xu, Yong-chang To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 20/2/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 37)
    - Xu, Yong-chang To Peter H. L. Chang, [Nanking] 18/4/[n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 37)
  - Xue, Da-ke
    - Xue, Da-ke To Peter H. L. Chang, [Taiwan] 9/5/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 07.09)
  - Yan, Bao-hang
    - Yan, Bao-hang To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 19/2/[n.y.], (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 38)
    - Yan Bao-hang To Peter H. L. Chang, Shanghai [n. d.], (3 photos ) (Box 06, Folder 08.07)
  - Yan, Ming-fu
    - Yan, Ming-fu To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 6/6/1990, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.07)
  - Yan, Ming-guang
    - Yan, Ming-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Shanghai 15/9/1990, (2 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.07)
    - Yan Ming-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Shanghai 15/9/1990, (2 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.07)
    - Yan, Ming-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Shanghai 6/12/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed and calling card ) (Box 06, Folder 08.07)
    - Yan Ming-guang To Peter H. L. Chang, Shanghai [n.d.], (Seven photos ) (Box 06, Folder 08.07)
  - Yan, Wei-cong
    - Yan, Wei-cong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 39)
    - Yan, Wei-cong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page, printed document ) (Box 04, Folder 39)
      [See Zhang Da-qian [Box7]]
  - Yang, Hu-cheng
    - Yang, Hu-cheng [also as Yang Hu-ch’eng] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An ] 11/1/[1937], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 40.01)
    - Yang, Hu-cheng To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 16/1/[1937], (2 page, autograph letter signed and 3 page [n.d.] handwritten draft proposals on national affairs ) (Box 04, Folder 40.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Yang Hu-cheng, [Xikou] 19/[n.m.]/[1937], (3 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 40.03)
  - Yang, Jing-hua
    - Yang, Jing-hua and Gao Qing-shan To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang [n.d.], (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 05.05)
  - Yang, Zhen-zhi
    - Yang, Zhen-zhi [also as Yang Cheng-chih] To H. L.Chang, [n.p.] 4/5/[n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 41)
  - Yang, Zheng-min
    - Yang, Zheng-min To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 30/3/1993, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.08)
  - Yin Shun Fashi
    - Yin Shun Fashi To Liu Yi-guang, [n.p.]7/2/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 43)
  - You, Jian-zhao
    - You, Jian-zhao [also as K.C. Yu, You Chian-chao] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 15/3/[1960], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 44.01)
    - You, Jian-zhao To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, Taipei 20/3/M76[1987], (1 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 44)
      [See Mei-ling Soong Chiang [Box 1, Folder 13.4]]
    - You, Jian-zhao To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] 20/2/M78[1989], (1 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 44)
    - You, Jian-zhao To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei]7/4/M78[1989], (1 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 04, Folder 44)
    - You, Jian-zhao To H. L.Chang, Taiwan 4/12/[n.y.], (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 44.01)
    - You, Jian-zhao To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 23/12/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 44)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 50 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Yu, [?]
    - Yu, [?] To Peter H. L. Chang, Pudong 3/7/M36 [1947], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 45)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 62-63 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Yu [?] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 18/5/ [n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter ) (Box 06, Folder 18)
  - Yu, Bin
    - Yu, Bin [also as Yu Pin] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 8/5/[n.y.], (1 autograph calling card signed ) (Box 04, Folder 46)
  - Yu, Xue-zhong
    - Yu, Xue-zhong [also as Yu Hsueh Chung], et al To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 16/1/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 47)
    - Yu, Xue-zhong To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 25/2/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 47.01)
    - Yu Xue-zhong To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 24/4/ [n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 47.02)
    - Chang, H.L. To Yu Xue-zhong and others, [Xikou] 19/[n.m.]/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 47.03)
    - Chang, H.L. To Yu Xue-zhong, [Jingshang] 17/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 47.03)
  - Yu, Ye-sheng
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Yu Ye-sheng, [n.p.] 18/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 48)
  - Yu, You-ren
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Yu You-ren [also as Yu You-jen] et. al., [n.p.] 17/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 49)
  - Yu, Yun-chang, Yu Yun-zhao, Yu Yun-xian and Yu Yun-wen
    - Yu, Yun-chang and Yu Yun-zhao and Yu Yun-xian and Yu Yun-wen To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 30/5/1990, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.09)
  - Zang, Shi-yi
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zang Shi-yi [also as Tzang Shih-yi], [n.p.] 9/2/[n.y.], (7 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 50)
  - Zeng, Bao-sun
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Zeng Bao-sun, Peitou 3/11/1961, (1 page, typed letter draft (with 1 copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 51.01)
    - Zeng, Bao-sun To Edith Chao Chang, Taipei7/12/1961, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 51.01)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Zeng Bao-sun, Peitou 11/12/ 1961, (1 page, typed letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 51.02)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Zeng Bao-sun, Peitou 29/12/1961, (1 page, typed letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 51.02)
    - Zeng, Bao-sun [also as Tzeng Pao-sun] To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipie] 14/1/1962, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 51.02)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Zeng Bao-sun, [n.p.] 20/1/1962, (1 page, typed letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 51.02)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Zeng Bao-sun, Peitou 27/4/1962, (1 page, typed letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 51.02)
    - Zeng, Bao-sun To Edith Chao Chang, Taipei 13/5/1963, (1 leaf; 4 printed documents ) (Box 04, Folder 51.03)
    - Zeng, Bao-sun To Edith Chao Chang, Taipei 13/5/1963, (15 page, printed document ) (Box 04, Folder 51.03)
    - Zeng, Bao-sun To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipie] [n.d.], (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 04, Folder 51.04)
    - Zeng, Bao-sun To [Edith Chao Chang], [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, typed letter (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 51.05)
    - Zeng, Bao-sun To [Edith Chao Chang], [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, typed document ) (Box 04, Folder 51.05)
  - Zeng, Kuo-qing
    - Zeng, Kuo-qing [also as Tzeng K’uo-ch’ing] To H. L.Chang, [n.p.] 1/4/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 52)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, pages 34-35 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Zeng, Yue-nong
    - Zeng, Yue-nong [also as Tseng Yueh-nung] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 4/5/M51 [1962], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 53)
      [Note: Chang Personal Album, pages 54-55 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Zeng, Yue-nong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 25/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 53)
      [Note: Chang Personal Album, page 52 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Zhang, Dai-Qian
    - Yan Wei-Cong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] [n. d.], (2 page, regarding anniversary exhibition of Zhang Dai-qian. ) (Box 04, Folder 54.01)
    - Yan Wei-Cong To Peter H. L. Chang, Washington, D. C. 1991/1992, (2 printed invitations to Zhang Dai-Qian memorial exhibition ) (Box 04, Folder 54)
  - Zhang, De-liang
    - Zhang, De-liang and Zhou Yi To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang 28/12/1990, (8 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 05.06)
  - Zhang, Guan-ying
    - Zhang Guan-ying To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.]4[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 10.03)
    - Zhang Guan-ying To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 30/4 [n.y.], (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 10.04)
    - Zhang Guan-ying To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p] [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 10.04)
    - Zhang Guan-ying To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 17/5 [n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 06, Folder 10.05)
    - Zhang Guan-ying To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 18/5 [n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 06, Folder 10.05)
  - Zhang, Ji-zhong
    - Zhang, Ji-zhong [also as Chang Chi-chung] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 29/5/1963, (8 leaf, autograph document signed ) (Box 04, Folder 55.01)
    - Zhang, Ji-zhong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (8 leaf, autograph document signed ) (Box 04, Folder 55.02)
    - Zhang, Ji-zhong To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (4 page, typed document ) (Box 04, Folder 55.03)
    - Zhang, Ji-zhong To Mr.. and Mrs..Peter H. L. Chang, Pasadena CA 17/3/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 55.04)
  - Zhang, Jie-qian
    - Zhang, Jie-qian [also as Chang Chieh-chian] To Peter H. L. Chang, U.S.A. 30/4/1990, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 56)
    - Zhang, Jie-qian [also as Chang Chieh-chian] To Peter H. L. Chang, U.S.A. 29/5/1994, (1 page, fax ) (Box 04, Folder 56)
  - Zhang, Jing-hua
    - Zhang, Jing-hua To Peter H. L. Chang, Jiangyin 11/6/1990, (2 page, autograph letter signed and two photos and handwritten note ) (Box 06, Folder 01.11)
  - [Changsan?]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To [Changsan?], [n.p.] March 16 [n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 37, Folder 03.04)
  - Zhang, Mu-tao
    - Zhang, Mu-tao [also as Chang Mu-tau] To [Peter H. L. Chang], [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph document signed ) (Box 04, Folder 57.01)
    - Zhang, Mu-tao To [Peter H. L. Chang], [Taiwan] [n.d.], (3 leaf, autograph document ) (Box 04, Folder 57.01)
    - Zhang, Mu-tao To Zhang Yan-fo, [n.p.] 3/11/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 57.02)
  - Zhang, Qi-Wei
    - Zhang, Qi-Wei [also as Chang Ch’i-wei] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 24/2/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 58)
  - Zhang, Qun
    - Zhang, Qun [also as Chang Chun] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Taipei] 6/2/[1954], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 59.01)
      [Note: Chang’s Personal Album, pages 48-49 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Qun, [n.p., n.d.]/[n.m.]/M43 [1954], (1 leaf autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 59.01)
    - Zhang Qun To. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 congratulatory greeting card ) (Box 04, Folder 59.02)
    - Zhang, Qun To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.]/[n.m.]/1988, (1 envelope ) (Box 04, Folder 59.02)
    - Zhang, Qun To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.]/[n.m.]/1990, (1 envelope ) (Box 04, Folder 59.02)
    - Zhang, Qun To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chengdu] 19/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 59.02)
      [Note: Chang’s Personal Album, page 17 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Zhang, Qun To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 6/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 59.02)
      [Note: Chang’s Personal Album, page 18 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Zhang, Qun To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 27/10/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 59.02)
      [Note: Chang’s Personal Album, page 19 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Qun, [n.p.] 19/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 59.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Qun, [n.p.] 16/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 59.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Qun, [n.p.] 8/11/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 59.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Qun, [n.p.] 23/[n.m.]/[n.y.] (Box 04, Folder 59.03)
      [2 page, autograph letter (draft)]
    - Zhang, Qun To Mo De-hui, [n.p.] 6/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 59.04)
  - Zhang, Shou-fang
    - Zhang, Shou-fang [also as Chang Shou-fang] To Peter H. L. Chang, Xi An 30/4/[n.y.], (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 60)
      [Note: See San Yu Tang [Box 6, Folder 13]]
    - Zhang, Shou-fang To H. L Chang, [n.p., n.d.]/4/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 60)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Shou-fang, [n.p.] 17/5/[n.y.], (3 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 60)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Shou-fang, [n.p.] 18/5/[n.y.], (3 leaf, autograph letter (draft) ) (Box 04, Folder 60)
    - Dong, Ying-bin To Zhang Shou-fang, [n.p.] 22/4/[n.y.], (1 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 60)
      [Enclosed in the letter from Zhang Shou-fang to H. L. Chang on 30/4/[n.y.], see San Yu Tang [Box 6, Folder 13]]
    - Zhang, Shou-fang To Dong Ying-bin, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 60)
      [See San Yu Tang [Box 6 Folder 13]; Enclosed in the letter from Zhang Shou-fang to H. L. Chang on 30/4/[n.y.]]
    - Ma, Yi To Zhang Shou-fang, [n.p.] 14/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 60)
  - Zhang, Yan-fo
    - Zhang, Yan-fo [also as Chang Yan-fo] To Peter H. L. Chang, Xinzhu [n.d.]/10/M36 [1947], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 11/11/M36 [1947], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, Jingshang [n.d.]/11/M36 [1947], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 6/5/[n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 1/6/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 19/10/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 20/11/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 25/12/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed (with list of purchases) ) (Box 04, Folder 61.01)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.02)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.02)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.02)
    - Zhang, Yan-fo To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 61.02)
  - Zhang, Yan-yuan
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhang Yan-yuan [also as Chang Yan-yuan], [Taipei] 30/10/[n.y.], (2 page autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 62)
    - Zhang, Yan-yuan To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 23/12/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 62)
      [Note: Chang’s Personal Album, page 53 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Zhao, Bao-shan
    - Zhao, Bao-shan To Peter H. L. Chang, Tianjin 26/1/1987, (1 autograph card signed (photocopy) ) (Box 06, Folder 07.10)
  - Zhao, Bing-qing
    - Zhao, Bing-qing [also as Chao Ping-ch’ing] et al To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (3 page, autograph letter signed, with signatures of Shang Yan-nian, Guo Zheng-jia ) (Box 04, Folder 63)
  - Zhao, Heng-yu
    - Zhao, Heng-yu [also as Chau Heng-yu] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 28/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 64)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 51 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Zhao, Long-wen
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhao Long-wen [also as Chau Lung-wen], [n.p.] 19/2/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 65)
    - Zhao, Long-wen To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 1/4/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 65)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 37 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Zhao, Meng-wan
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Zhao Meng-wan [also as Chau Meng-wen], [n.p.]7/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 66)
  - Zhao, Shuang-cheng
    - Zhao, Shuang-cheng (????-should be in documents or printed materials) To Peter H. L. Chang, Shenyang [n.d.], (2 calling cards, with 2 printed page a resume and information ) (Box 06, Folder 05.07)
  - Zhao, Yang
    - Zhao, Yang To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 3/7/1990, (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.10)
  - Zhao, Yi
    - Zhao, Yi [also as Chau Yi] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 9/3/[1937], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 67.01)
    - Zhao, Yi To H. L.Chang, [n.p.] 17/3/[1937], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 67.02)
    - Zhao, Yi To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 21/2/[1946], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 67.03)
  - Zhao Yi Di
    - Zhao Yi-di To Edith Chang, [n.p.] 3/2/1940, (1 page telegram ) (Box 04, Folder 68)
  - Zheng, Bi-jun
    - Zheng, Bi-jun To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 23/8/1993, (6 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 08.11)
  - Zheng, Jie-min